//This JS file is the array containing the quiz questions. 
var questions = [
  {
    "question": "What is a noun in this sentence?   After the children ate the cake, they played some games.",
    "option1": "ate",
    "option2": "games",
    "option3": "played",
    "option4": "they",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Subject in this sentence?   I helped Jason with his spelling words.",
    "option1": "I",
    "option2": "Jason",
    "option3": "spelling",
    "option4": "helped",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a verb in this sentence?  The beautiful blue fairy grants his wish.",
    "option1": "beautiful",
    "option2": "fairy",
    "option3": "grants",
    "option4": "wish",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a Modifier in this sentence?  Old witches are villians in many fairy tales.",
    "option1": "witches",
    "option2": "Old",
    "option3": "villains",
    "option4": "are",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a preposition in this sentence?  The children enjoy playing outside on warm summer days.",
    "option1": "children",
    "option2": "enjoy",
    "option3": "summer",
    "option4": "on",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Direct Object in this sentence?  We played a game of touch football after school.",
    "option1": "We",
    "option2": "played",
    "option3": "school",
    "option4": "game",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is an adverb in this sentence?  The jovial students work happily on their school project.",
    "option1": "jovial",
    "option2": "students",
    "option3": "school",
    "option4": "happily",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Predicate Adjective in this sentence?  The woman's golden, ringlet-filled tresses were beautiful.",
    "option1": "golden",
    "option2": "beautiful",
    "option3": "woman's",
    "option4": "tresses",
    "answer": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Indirect Object in this sentence?  Write your uncle a little note, please.",
    "option1": "uncle",
    "option2": "little",
    "option3": "note",
    "option4": "please",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Predicate Nominative in this sentence?  My favorite dog was a big black poodle.",
    "option1": "favorite",
    "option2": "dog",
    "option3": "black",
    "option4": "poodle",
    "answer": "4"
  },
];
